# AIDIL FITRAH ROMADHONI

Tulungagung - Rejotangan - Pakisrejo, 66293· +6289683322400 doni.smpn1gmail.com · linkedin: aidil-fitrah-romadhoni

I am a student who has been learning to become a programmer for the past two years. I have been studying UI/UX design, Web Development, as well as improving my communication skills to be able to effectively manage teams.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**2023/10 – 2024/02 BACKEND DEV,** HALTECH

- I am currently studying GoLang, which will be utilized as an API to connect to a Postgres database, ultimately consumed by a Flutter frontend.
- I also understand the concept of a database and API usage

2024/02 - NOW

#### **FULLSTACK WEB DEV, HALTECH**

• Creating a website using Firebase that will be able to output real-time data, including IoT data that provides real-time updates on the website.

#### **EDUCATION**

2019/07 – 2022/06 JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL, SMP Negeri 1 Rejotangan

General education

2022/07 – NOW

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL, SMK Negeri 1 Boyolangu

Language, Organization, and Programming

# **SKILLS**

## GENERAL

Web Dev

I have significant experience in building websites, especially using Firebase as a backend for real-time data integration and other features. I am more comfortable working on the frontend, with a strong understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I can create responsive and interactive user interfaces using these technologie

## Video Editing

I have intermediate skills in video editing. While I may not be an expert, I am quite familiar with the editing process, including cutting clips, adding basic effects, and adjusting audio. I use software like Capcut to produce videos that meet basic production needs.

## Languages

• Indonesian:

My native language, which I use daily for both spoken and written communication.

### English

I have a basic understanding of English, capable of comprehending and communicating in certain situations, though not fluently.

# Technical

• HTML, CSS, JavaScript:

My expertise lies in frontend development using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I can create visually appealing and functional interfaces and understand the principles of responsive design.

# • Capcut:

I am quite familiar with using Capcut for video editing. I can handle moderately complex editing tasks, including storyboarding and adding essential elements to produce viewable content.